let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "what is full form of HTML?",
    answer: "B. Hyper Text Markup Language",
    options: [
      "A. Hyperlink Text Marking Language",
      "B. Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "C. Hyper text marking up language",
      "D. Hyperlink Markup language",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the primary programming language used in Data Science?",
    answer: "B. Python",
    options: ["A. Java", "B. Python", "C. C++", "D. Ruby"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What does the acronym 'SQL' stand for?",
    answer: "A. Structured Query Language",
    options: [
      "A. Structured Query Language",
      "B. System Query Language",
      "C. Structured Quick Language",
      "D. Syntax Query Language",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "In which phase of the data science process is data cleaning typically done?",
    answer: "C. Data Preprocessing",
    options: [
      "A. Data Collection",
      "B. Data Visualization",
      "C. Data Preprocessing",
      "D. Model Deployment",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "What is the main purpose of a data visualization tool like Tableau?",
    answer: "D. Create visual representations of data",
    options: [
      "A. Store data",
      "B. Clean data",
      "C. Analyze text",
      "D. Create visual representations of data",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: " What is a 'Random Forest' in Data Science?",
    answer: "C. An ensemble of decision trees",
    options: [
      "A. A type of neural network",
      "B. A clustering algorithm",
      "C. An ensemble of decision trees",
      "D. A type of data visualization",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "Which of the following is a commonly used library in Python for data manipulation?",
    answer: "A. Pandas",
    options: ["A. Pandas", "B. TensorFlow", "C. PyTorch", "D. Seaborn"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is overfitting in the context of machine learning?",
    answer: "A. When a model learns the noise in the data",
    options: [
      "A. When a model learns the noise in the data",
      "B. When a model fits data perfectly",
      "C. When a model underperforms",
      "D. When a model fits only part of the data",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is a type of classification algorithm?",
    answer: "D. Support Vector Machine",
    options: [
      "A. K-means Clustering",
      "B. Principal Component Analysis",
      "C. Linear Regression",
      "D. Support Vector Machine",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which tool is commonly used for big data processing?",
    answer: "B. Apache Hadoop",
    options: ["A. MySQL", "B. Apache Hadoop", "C. PostgreSQL", "D. Tableau"],
  },
];
